# KIP SCHETNAN

Northfield, MN 55057 ● 5074031576 ● kipdougschetnan@gmail.com

## Website, Portfolio, Profiles

- https://kipschetnan.github.io/My-Portfolio/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/kip-schetnan-185860249/

### **Education**

No Degree: Computer Science

Gustavus Adolphus College - Saint Peter, MN

Left Gustavus after one year and decided to enroll in the Full Stack Web Development through the University of Minnesota.

**Web Development Bootcamp Certificate**: Expected in 02/2023 **University of Minnesota - Twin Cities** - Minneapolis, MN

## **Professional Summary**

Accommodating Pro Shop Representative possessing first-rate customer service and multitasking skills. Bringing some hands-on experience assisting with scheduling and retail sales of golf course's pro shop. Accountable and responsible individual with in-depth knowledge of golf rules and etiquette. On top of that, experience in the computer science world with a year of classes in high school and a year in college, then taking on a web development boot camp and developing many skills that are presented within the boot camp.

#### Skills

- Customer Experience
- Full Stack Web Development experience
- Problem-Solving

- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Attention to Detail
- Active Listening

## **Work History**

Golf Pro Shop Employee, 05/2022 to 11/2022

Willingers Golf Club - Northfield, MN

- Greeted customers, helped locate merchandise and suggested suitable options.
- Answered customer questions about products and services, helped locate merchandise and promoted key items.
- Checked pricing, scanned items, applied discounts and printed receipts to ring up customers.
- Listened to customer needs and desires to identify and recommend optimal products.
- Made sure each customer was checked in and ready to golf.

Grounds Maintenance Crew, 05/2022 to 09/2022

#### Summit Golf - Northfield, MN

- Cleared public and private areas of debris before and after events.
- Used trimmers and chainsaws for grounds maintenance, brush clearing and tree removal and thinning.
- Repaired ground structures regularly, sticking to schedules and meeting facility needs.
- Maintained routine landscaping schedules to boost lawn health.
- Mowed greens, fairways and tee boxes on a daily basis.

### Landscaping Crew Member, 06/2021 to 08/2021

#### Yard Cents - Burnsville, MN

- Trimmed greenery, shrubs and hedges to maintain uniform appearance.
- Performed planting, watering, mulching and edging of lawns.
- Handled hedge, bush and shrub trimming.
- Removed weeds, hazards and debris from common pathways to improve usability.

#### **Day Stocker**, 07/2018 to 02/2019

#### Cub Foods - Northfield, MN

- Unloaded arriving product stock and moved to store display areas.
- Helped customers complete purchases by moving heavy items, collecting payments and bagging purchases.
- Readied items for sales floor stocking by affixing tags and preparing shelf labels.
- Stayed current on available products, store promotions and customer service policies to better serve shoppers.

## Certifications

Full Stack Web Development, University of Minnesota - August, 2022 - February, 2023